<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Twonky</string>

    <string name="menu_help">Help</string>
    <string name="menu_about">About &#8230;</string>
    <string name="menu_exit">Exit</string>

    <string name="helpalert_title">Help</string>
    <string name="helpalert_message1">THIS IS THE GAME OF TWONKY. IN IT YOU PRETEND TO BE A SPACE EXPLORER WHO HAS
    LANDED ON A HOSTILE PLANET.\n\n
    CAPTURED BY THE UNFRIENDLY NATIVES, YOU ARE TOSSED INTO A LARGE PRISON ALONG WITH A FEROCIOUS TWONKY.\n\n
    A TWONKY IS A HORRIBLE CREATURE WHO WILL CATCH YOU AND ABSORB YOUR BODY INTO HIS IF HE GETS CLOSER THAN TWO UNITS
    AWAY FROM YOU.</string>
    <string name="helpalert_message2">IN THE INTEREST OF FAIR PLAY, YOU ARE GIVEN A ZAP GUN THAT WILL TEMPORARILY
    CHASE THE TWONKY AWAY.\n\n
    ALSO, IF YOU CAN MAKE IT TO THE SPECIAL OBJECTIVE SQUARE BEFORE BEING ABSORBED, YOU WILL BE SET FREE.\n\n
    AFTER YOU MOVE, YOU WILL BE INFORMED OF YOUR DISTANCE FROM THE OBJECTIVE SQUARE AS WELL AS FROM THE TWONKY.</string>
    <string name="helpalert_message3">THERE ARE SEVERAL OTHER OBJECTS IN THE MAZE WHICH ARE OF INTEREST\n\n
    THERE ARE TWENTY RELOCATION SQUARES. THESE SQUARES SEND YOU TO SOME OTHER PLACE IN THE MAZE.\n\n
    THERE ARE TWENTY IMPREGNABLE SQUARES WHICH YOU CANNOT ENTER.\n\n
    THERE IS ONE SUPER DEADLY AUTOMATIC KILL SQUARE WHICH ENDS YOUR ORDEAL QUICKLY AND PAINLESSLY.\n\n
    THAT\'S IT &#8230; TRY TO ENJOY IT!
    </string>

    <string name="helpalert_button_PLAY">Play</string>
    <string name="helpalert_button_MORE">More</string>

    <string name="aboutalert_title">About</string>
    <string name="aboutalert_message">Twonky is a simple text game. It\'s based on code ported from an early
    terminal-style computer, the DEC-PDP-8, written in BASIC and ported to the Apple II.\n\nby:
    Mark Capella\nmarkcapella@twcny.rr.com\nirc nick:capella</string>
    <string name="aboutalert_button_OK">OK</string>

    <string name="logTextTitle">.</string>
    <string name="cmdTextTitle">Enter a command and press Done &#8230;</string>

    <string name="exit_toast">&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt; schlooooorp &gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;</string>

</resources>
